hackerrank.com 2019-09-07

# HackerRank

### HackerRank Privacy Policy

Data privacy is important to HackerRank, and when it comes to your data, we’re committed to protecting it and providing transparency about the information we collect from you and how we use it. This Privacy Policy is designed to let you know the information we collect about you on our websites (the “Websites”), including from individuals who register to use the HackerRank online community for software developers (the “HackerRank Community”), and individuals who use the HackerRank for Work service. This Privacy Policy describes HackerRank’s privacy practices in relation to the use of the Websites, and the related applications and services offered by HackerRank (collectively, the “Services”), as well as individuals’ choices regarding use, access and correction of personal information.In this Privacy Policy, the terms “HackerRank,” “We” and “Us” refer to Interviewstreet Incorporation, a Delaware corporation doing business as HackerRank

#### Types of Data Collected

HackerRank collects, processes, and retains information about you when you visit the Websites or use the Services. You may choose to provide HackerRank with information, such as your name, email address, company information, street address, telephone number, or other information, to use the Services or so we can follow up with you after your visit. If you choose to participate in the HackerRank Community, you may choose to provide us with additional information such as social media profiles, education information, experience, and other information. Certain data elements requested of you by the Websites are “mandatory” or “required,” and failure to provide this data may make it impossible for HackerRank to provide its Services to you. In cases where requested data elements are not mandatory or required, you may choose not to provide the requested data without any consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Services. We may combine other publicly available information with the information that you provide to us to enhance and optimize our Websites and Services for you. HackerRank may observe your activities, interactions, preferences, and other computer and connection information (such as IP address and geographic location) relating to your use of the Websites and the Services. HackerRank may also use log files, cookies and similar technologies to collect information about the pages you view, links you click on, and other actions you may take when accessing the Websites and Services. For more information about our use of these technologies, please see the Cookies section below. We may collect and store this information and combine this information with other personal information you may have provided.

#### HackerRank for Work Service Data

HackerRank for Work customers may upload data to the HackerRank for Work hosted Service. HackerRank will not share or distribute any such customer data except as provided in the contractual agreement between HackerRank and customer for the provision of the HackerRank for Work Service, or as may be required by law. If a HackerRank for Work customer is located within the European Economic Area, the customer is the Controller with respect to the HackerRank for Work data, and HackerRank is a Processor.

#### Use of Collected Data

HackerRank uses the information we collect about you to:

  * Provide you with the Websites and Services, together with any support you may request;
  * Respond to your inquiries or fulfill your requests;
  * Diagnose Website and Service technical problems;
  * Send you information that we believe may be of interest to you, such as Service announcements, newsletters, educational materials, and event information;
  * Send you administrative information such as notices related to the Services or policy changes;
  * Understand how the Websites and Services are being used in order to enhance and optimize them;
  * Personalize your experience on the Websites;
  * Prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate fraudulent or illegal activity; and
  * As described to you at the point of collection of the information.

#### Processing the Data

The information collected by HackerRank is stored and processed by HackerRank’s sub-processor, Amazon Web Services (“AWS”), leveraging AWS data centers located within the continental United States. Processing of the information collected about you is only undertaken for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Processing Details

##### Analytics

The third-party services described in this section enable HackerRank to monitor and analyze Website and Service traffic.

 _MixPanel (MixPanel Inc.)_

MixPanel is an analytics service provided by Mixpanel Inc.Information collected: Cookies and usage data.Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://mixpanel.com/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://mixpanel.com/optout/)

 _Google Analytics (Google Inc.)_

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. Google utilizes the information collected to track and examine the use of the Websites and Services to prepare reports that may be used for optimization of the Websites and Services.Information collected: Cookies and usage data.Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

##### Displaying Content from External Platforms

The third-party service described in this section enables HackerRank to display content to you on the Websites that is hosted on an external third party platform. This type of service may collect web traffic data in order to optimize delivery of the content on the Websites.

 _YouTube Video (Google Inc.)_

YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows the Websites and Services to incorporate content on its pages that is hosted on YouTube.Information collected: Cookies and usage data.Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

##### Geolocation

 _Geolocation (HackerRank Websites)_

The Websites may collect and use location information in order to provide location-based services to you.Most browsers and devices provide tools to opt out from this feature by default.Information collected: geographic location.

##### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

The third-party service described in this section enables HackerRank to display content to you on the Websites that is hosted on an external third party platform. This type of service may collect web traffic data in order to optimize delivery of the content on the Websites.

 _Facebook Like Button and Social Widgets (Facebook, Inc.)_

Information collected: Cookies and usage data. Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

 _Twitter Tweet Button and Social Widgets (Twitter)_

Information collected: Cookies and usage data.Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/privacy)

##### Registration and Authentication for the HackerRank Community

The third-party services described in this section enable the Websites and Services to register, identify and authenticate you in order to access dedicated Services.

 _Facebook Authentication (Facebook, Inc.)_

Information collected: authentication data as specified in the Facebook privacy policy.Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/help/405977429438260)

 _GitHub Authentication (GitHub Inc.)_

Information collected: authentication data as specified in the GitHub privacy policy.Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://help.github.com/articles/github-privacy-statement/)

 _Google OAuth (Google Inc.)_

Information collected: authentication data as specified in the Google OAuth privacy policy.Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://developers.google.com/accounts/docs/OAuth2)

 _LinkedIn Authentication (LinkedIn Corporation)_

Information collected: authentication data as specified in the LinkedIn privacy policy.Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy)

#### How We Disclose Your Data

We do not sell, lease, rent or give away the information collected about You without your permission. We only disclose your information as described below. If we disclose your information, we require those we share it with to comply with adequate privacy and confidentiality requirements, and security standards.

##### HackerRank Community

If you are a HackerRank Community member, we may list your username on a leader board if you participate in a CodeSprint. We may also share information about you with a potential employer if you opt for your information to be shared in order to connect with HackerRank Jobs and CodeSprint sponsor companies.

##### Service Providers Processing Data on Our Behalf

We may use contractors and service providers to process the information collected about you on our behalf for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We contractually require service providers to keep information secure and confidential and we do not allow our data processors to disclose your information to others without our authorization, or to use it for their own purposes. However, if you have an independent relationship with these service providers their privacy statements will apply.

##### Law Enforcement

In certain instances, it may be necessary for HackerRank to disclose the information that we’ve collected about you to government officials or otherwise as required by applicable law. No personal data will be disclosed to any law enforcement agency or governmental agency except in response to:

  * A subpoena, warrant or other process issued by a court of competent jurisdiction;
  * A legal process having the same consequence as a court-issued request for information, in that if HackerRank were to refuse to provide such information, it would be in breach of local law, and it or its officers, executives or employees would be subject to liability for failing to honor such legal process; or
  * Where such disclosure is necessary for HackerRank to enforce its legal rights pursuant to the laws of the jurisdiction from which such information was gathered.

#### Cookies and Similar Technologies

A cookie is a commonly used automated data collection tool. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or device by websites that you visit or HTML-formatted emails you open, in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently. We may use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, or other similar technologies on the Websites to, among other things:

  * Authenticate you as a HackerRank Community member or HackerRank for Work user;
  * Collect statistics regarding your usage of the Websites;
  * Tailor information presented to you based on your usage of the Websites;
  * Help provide additional functionality to the Websites; and
  * Analyze use of our Services.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. If a cookie blocking setting is selected on your browser, however, you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website or to receive certain Services.

#### Do-Not-Track

There are different ways you can prevent tracking of your online activity. One of them is setting a preference in your browser that alerts websites you visit that you do not want them to collect certain information about you. This is referred to as a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) signal. Please note that our Websites may not recognize or take action in response to DNT signals from your browser.

#### Managing Your Data

We retain the information that we collect about you for as long as your HackerRank Community or HackerRank for Work account is active or as needed to provide you Services. We also retain and use the information collected about you as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent and detect fraud, and enforce our agreements. We store the information collected about you for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which we collect it.

#### Accessing, Updating, Correcting or Deleting Your Data

You are able to view and update much of the information collected about you through your HackerRank Community account, or HackerRank for Work account. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you Services, contact us via the information below. We will respond to your request to access or delete your information within 30 days. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

HackerRank   
Attn: Privacy   
700 E. El Camino Real, Suite 300   
Mountain View, CA 94041   
United States 

Via email: [support@hackerrank.com](mailto:support@hackerrank.com) with “Privacy” in the subject line

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

HackerRank reserves the right to revise or modify this Privacy Policy. In such event, we will post a prominent notice on the Websites prior to the change becoming effective.
